

Apostolos Gouvalas Full-stack Web Developer

Full-stack developer with over 7 years of experience in PHP, SQL, and JavaScript, among other languages. With attention to detail and a passion for problem-solving, I am eager to contribute my skills to dynamic and challenging projects.

□ apo.gouv@gmail.com

+30-697 8811 469

cubedesigns.gr

• Thessaloniki, Greece

SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/apostolos-gouvalas

github.com/ApoGouv

EDUCATION

MS in Mobile and Web Computing

2016 - 2018

[Distinction]

International Hellenic University (Thessaloniki, Greece)

 Digital Systems Degree, majoring in "Communication and Network Systems"

2004 - 2013

University of Piraeus - Department of Digital Systems (Piraeus, Athens, Greece)

LANGUAGES

Greek [Native language]
English [Proficiency of Michigan & IELTS 7.5]
Spanish [A2 in progress]

SOFTWARE & TOOLS

VSCode, Git, Linux, Windows, cPanel, etc.

HOBBIES

Cycling, Dancing Salsa/ Kizomba, Sudoku, Rock Music

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Web Developer

Nov 2017 - Present | Mental Media (former MultiHosting)

- Development of e-commerce websites using platforms such as OpenCart, CS-Cart, PrestaShop, WooCommerce, etc., integrating custom functionalities and ERP programs.
- Website development including portfolios, corporate sites, personal websites, etc., using platforms such as WordPress, Joomla, etc.
- Contribution to various company projects utilizing technologies such as WHMCS, Laravel, vBulletin, Joomla, etc.

Front-end Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017 | PSDGator

 Converted design mockups from PSD or AI files to valid HTML and CSS, or WordPress themes.

Full-stack Web Developer

Dec 2015 - Present | Freelance

 Development of Websites and e-shops, as well as custom solutions according to customer requirements.

Front-end Web Developer

Apr 2014 - May 2014 | igraphics.gr

 User interface development, based on supplied graphic mockups, for applications to visualize the results of the 2014 Italian European Parliament Elections and display past Italian election results, using valid HTML, CSS, and jQuery.

CERTIFICATES

JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP, etc.

2017 - 2024 | Udemy

JavaScript Essentials

Build a Social Network from Scratch:
JavaScript PHP + MySQL

The Complete Node.js Developer
Course (2nd Edition)

Oct 09, 2017

The Complete JavaScript Course:
Build a Real-World Project

Sep 11, 2017

Aug 14, 2017